Guide to the Susie Bright papers and On Our Backs records, 1978-2013.
Bright, Susie papers and On Our Backs records
- Series III. Writings
  - Miscellaneous Writings
    - Penthouse Forum Articles, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "Lingerie Fever" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "A Matter of Black and White" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "New Age Porn" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "Raw Nerves" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "Red Wings" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "Smoker is the Funniest Porn Flick Ever Made" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "Some Like it Taut" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "Susie's Farewell" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "Taboo Buster" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "This Year's Model" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "This Year's Winners" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "The Trouble with Traci" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "What do Women Want" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "What I Did on My Summer Vacation" (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - "Working on the Sex Line" (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - "Nothing but the Girl: the Blatant Lesbian Image", 1995 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      contracts to be in publication
    - Susie's Articles on Porn (Box 16, Folder 21)
      mixed booklet, AVN "A History of Black Adult Video"
    - RESTRICTED Erotic Film and Video Survey questionnaires and results originals, 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - RESTRICTED Erotic Film and Video Survey questionnaires and results copies (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - RESTRICTED Erotic Film and Video Survey loose questionnaires (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Best American Erotica
    - Best American Erotica Contracts, 1993; 1 (Box 17)
    - Best American Erotica Contracts, 1994; 2 (Box 17)
    - Best American Erotica Contracts, 1995; 3 (Box 17)
    - Best American Erotica Contracts, 1996; 4 (Box 17)
    - Best American Erotica Contracts, 1997; 5 (Box 17)
    - Best American Erotica Contracts, 1998-1999; 6 (Box 17)
    - Best American Erotica Contracts, 2000; 7 (Box 17)
    - Best American Erotica Reader Surveys, 1995-1997; 8 (Box 17)
  - Media Books
    - Adam: "Girls and Girls Together" (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Chronicle: "The X-Rated Intellectual" (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Hustler: "Confessions of a Teenage Dyke (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - E. Bay express: "The Good, The Bad, and the Uppity", November 5, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - The New York Native: "Year of the Lustful Lesbian", July 1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Bay Area Reporter: "Lesbian Erotica Comes of Age", September 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - The Body Politics: "At Last!", November 1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Gaylife: "Mag Celebrates the Lustful Lesbian", August 16, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - The Advocate: "'Hot and Wet' The New LEsbian Sex Press", January 22, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - The Village Voice: "What We Talk About When We Talk About Dildos", March 5, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Playboy Forum: "A Hot New Magazine For Lusty Lesbians", June 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Ms.: "Toys for Free Grown-Ups", August 1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - The Whole Earth Review: "The Bloom in Women's Erotica", 1986 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - "Lesbian Strippers", December 1986 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Penthouse Letters: "X-Rated View", December 1986 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "Lesbians Urge 'Safe Sex' as AIDS Precaution", December 30, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Velvet: "On Her Back", 1988 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Lambda Rising Book Project: "Surveying Contemporary Lesbian Erotica", 1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Gay Community News: "Porn, Incest and the Uses of the Neurotic", July 31, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Next: "Susie Sexpert Speaks", August 10, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Next: "Sex Positive", August 10, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Bay Windows: "Lesbian Sex: What Are Women Up To?", August 1988 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Guide: "Sexpert", 1988 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Utne Reader: "When Women Talk About Sex", September 1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Review of Herotica, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Screw: "Plato's Retread", October 17, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Sojourn R: "Exploring Our Sexual Fantasies: Women's Erotica", October 1988 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Boston Globe, November 27, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - New York native: "Bright Herotica", November 7, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Gay Community News: "Sexperts Urge More, Better Sex in S.F.", November 20-26, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Los Angeles Frontiers: "Local Girl Makes Good", March 1989 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - L.A. Times: "'Machine': A Teutonic Slant on Lesbianism", June 2, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Playboy: "Burning Desires: Sex in America", July 1989 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "What We Can Learn From Dirty Movies", September 15, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - San Francisco Weekly: "Street Talk", September 1989 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - The San Francisco Bay Guardian: "How to Read a Dirty Movie", September 13, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - San Francisco Sentinel: "Bright and Dirty", September 14, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "What We Can Learn From Dirty Movies", September 15, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Roxie Cinema: "How to Read a Dirty Movie", September 15-16, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Bay Area Reporter: "Lesbian Magazine Celebrates", September 21, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - The San Francisco Bay Times, October 1989 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Hustler's Erotic Video: "Susie's All Girl Action", October 1989 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - People: "If You Knew Susie Bright", January 30, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Los Angeles Times: "'How to Read a Dirty Movie' At the Nuart", February 1, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - LA Weekly: "How to Read a Dirty Movie", February 8, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Express: "How to Read a Dirty Movie", February 16, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Mother Jones: "Nasty Girls", February/March 1990 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Frisko: "Susie", March 1990 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Minnesota Daily and equal Time editorials and opinions, April 1990 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Lambda Book Report: "Susie's World", 1990 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Spectator: "Susie Trailblazer", 1990 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Dare: "Sex Talk From the Expert", 1990 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - The Village Voice: "Susie Sexpert's Lesbian Sex World", 1990 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - San Francisco Weekly: "Putting the Fun Back in Feminism", July 18, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Bay Area Reporter: "Pushing Our Sexual Boundaries", August 9, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Bay Area Reporter: "Pushing OUr Sexual Boundaries", August 9, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Outweek: "Dyke Cum-ings and Goings", August 15, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Chic: "The 3rd Degree", August 18, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - The Gourmet Club: "Book Nook", September 1990 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - The Washington Blade: "The Return of Susie Sexpert", September 7, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Screw: "Mating Sleazin'", September 17, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Image: "The Body Electric", October 7, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - The Women's Review of Books: "Words to Lust By", November 1990 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Outweek: "Sex and the Single Dyke", November 7, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Montreal Mirror: "Female Persuasions, November 8-15, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Left Field: "Healing the Wounds of Sexual Repression", December 1990 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Chicago Outline: "The Bright Side of Susie Bright, November 1990 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - The Austin Chronicle: "Susie Sexpert Explains It All to You", November 9, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Dallas Voice: "Leapin' Lesbians", November 14, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Gay Community News: "If You Knew Susie", November 18-24, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Outweek: "Gay and Pregnant", November 28, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - City On A Hill Press: Opinions, December 6, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - SF Weekly: "The Last Gasp", December 5, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Guardian: "Notes for the Burrowing Bookworm", December 5, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Rouge: "Susie Sexpert's Lesbian Sex World", 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Rolling Stone: "Walk on the Bright Side", January 24, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - San Francisco Chronicle: "Learning to think Rambunctiously", March 15, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Image: "Blood Brothers", May 15, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - MagazineWeek: "San Francisco Mags Battle Over Murder Case", May 20-24, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Esquire: "Cain and Abel in the Skin Trade", June 1991 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Daily News: "Sex and Death", July 7, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Los Angeles Times: "'Love 'Em, Leave 'Em' at Silent Movie, July 3, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Advocate: "What a Friend We Have In Dildos, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - City Pages: "Recapture the Flag", July 3, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - LA Weekly: "Film Picks of the Week", July 5, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - The Village Voice: "Guns N' Poses", July 16, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - GirlJock: "Susie Bright", 1991 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Image: "Strip Tea", October 27, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Esquire: "Women on Men: The Uneasy State of Masculinity Now", October 1991 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - NYQ: "Susie Bright Undresses Camille Paglia", November 10, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Image: "Tea and Hot Cross Buns", November 24, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Elle: "When Good Girls Have Bad Fantasies", November 1991 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - On Our Backs: "Alison Bechdel", November/December 1991 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - LinguaFranca: "Sexpertise", December 1991 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Articles on "Angry Women", December 1991-April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Entre Nous: "Susie Bright Undresses Camille Paglia", December 1991 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - The Advocate: "Using Their Anger", January 1992 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Elle: "Sex in the Computer Age", January 1992 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Seattle Weekly: "It's here, It's Queer, It's About Time", February 26, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - San Francisco Bay Times: "How About Those Music Awards", February 27, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Express: "Sex and the Single Reader", March 1992 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - LA Reader: "Reading: Why Don't We Do It On The Telephone", March 20, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - San Francisco Chronicle: "The Latest Dirt on Madonna Feud", March 26, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - SF Weekly: "Good Girl, Hot Sex", April 29, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - The Other Side: "Susie the Sexpert Comes to the Castro", April 30, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - SF Weekly: "Disc 3, April 29, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Esquire: "Sleeping With the Enemy", April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - SF Bay Area Reporter: "Uncensored Desires", April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - "The Erotic Aesthetic", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Panorama: "Let's Talk About Sex, Baby", April 3, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Gaze Newspaper: "Herotica 2", April 30, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - The Northwest Gay and Lesbian Reader: "New Colors to your Imagination", March/April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - Nina's Review of "Lesbian Sex World", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - Outlook: "Undressing Camille", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - The Bay Guardian: "Love in the Afternoon", May 6, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "Making Dirty Movies Bright", May 6, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - San Francisco Bay Times: "Schmoozy Bright", May 7, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - Lambda Book Report: "Herotica 2", May 1992 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    - Examiner: "Letters to the Editor", May 27, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 119)
    - The New York Times: "Increasing Our Dirty-Word Power: Why Yesterday's Smut is Today's Erotica", May 31, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 120)
    - GLHS Newsletter: "Did You See...?", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 121)
    - New York: "Sex in the 90s", June 8, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 122)
    - Small Press: "Sexual Reality", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 123)
    - San Francisco Chronicle: "Born-Again Feminism", June 2, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 124)
    - Voice: "Paper Chase", June 3, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 125)
    - Whole Earth Review: "Egg Sex", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 126)
    - Express: "Publisher's Row", June 1992 (Box 18, Folder 127)
    - Express: "I Got This Way From kissing Donahue", June 12, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 128)
    - City Pages: "She's Gonna Have It", June 17, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 129)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "Future Sex Ain't What It Used to Be", June 26, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 130)
    - Publishers Weekly: "A Niche Market Comes of Age", June 29, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 131)
    - Outlines: "Susie Bright's Sexual Reality", July 1992 (Box 18, Folder 132)
    - Arizona Community Echo: "Giving Gay Fiction a Rest", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 133)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "In GOP Eyes We All Are The Children", August 20, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 134)
    - Mama Bears: "Sex is Big Says California Essayist", August-September 1992 (Box 18, Folder 135)
    - Big and Tall bookstore advertisement with Susie Bright, September 15, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 136)
    - The Pink Paper: "Susie Bright's Sexual Reality", August 9, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 137)
    - Metro: "The Future's So Bright", August 23-September 2, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 138)
    - "The San Diego Review: "The Reality of Virtually Orgasmic Thoughts", September 1, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 139)
    - Lambda Book Report: "Susie Bright's Sexual Reality", September-October 1992 (Box 18, Folder 140)
    - LA Weekly: "Reading Picks of the Week", September 11-17, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 141)
    - USA Today: "Readers Turned on to Classy Books", September 10, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 142)
    - Daily 49er: "Sex Author on Campus to Show Book", September 17, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 143)
    - Image: "Can Feminists Wear Heels?", September 27, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 144)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "The Original Feminist?", September 30, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 145)
    - Masquerade Erotic Book Society: "Herotica 2", September-October 1992 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    - Empathy: "Susie Bright's Sexual Reality", 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 147)
    - SF Review of Books: "The Virtual Orgasm", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 148)
    - The Realist: "Dan Quayle's Dick", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 149)
    - Quim: "Hippy Chick", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 150)
    - Pleasure Guide: "Susie Bright's Sexual Reality", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - Express: "Tie Me Up, Bog Me Down", October 1992 (Box 18, Folder 152)
    - SF Weekly: "Dan Quayle, Sex Stud For Hire", October 14, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 153)
    - The Daily: "More Words of Wisdom From Susie Sexpert", October 29, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 154)
    - Adam: "Bright Writes", November 1992 (Box 18, Folder 155)
    - San Francisco Chronicle: "Where the Cultural Elite Meet", November 2, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 156)
    - Village Voice: "Waxing Philosophic", November 24, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 157)
    - Screw: "Not too Bright", November 30, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 158)
    - Argonaut Premiere Cover, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 159)
    - LA Reader: "What's Your Favorite material to Read to Your Kid(s)?", December 1992 (Box 18, Folder 160)
    - SF Review of Books: "A Pornographic Girl", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 161)
    - Chic: "You've Come a Long Way, Susie", December 1992 (Box 18, Folder 162)
    - The New York Times: "That Girl by the Stage, and Why She's Tere", December 20, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 163)
    - The Advocate: "Camille Paglia Defends Her Rotten Record", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 164)
    - Magical Blend: "Egg Sex", January 1993 (Box 18, Folder 165)
    - The San Francisco Examiner: "'Crying Game's' Last Laugh", January 17, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 166)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "Giving Away A Film's Secret", January 29, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 167)
    - OUT: "Honey I brought the Kid", February-March 1993 (Box 18, Folder 168)
    - Update Newspaper: "Constant Reader", February 10, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 169)
    - San Francisco erotic Dancer: "O'Farrell After Hours: The Safe Sex Classroom", February 1993 (Box 18, Folder 170)
    - Bay Times, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 171)
    - Inside the City: "SF's Most Powerful Women", March 1993 (Box 18, Folder 172)
    - Mondo 2000: "Susie Bright Talks with Lydia Lunch", March 1993 (Box 18, Folder 173)
    - "An Intimate Chat With Susie Bright", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 174)
    - Seattle Gay News: "Susie Sexpert Gives a Sexual State of the Union Address", March 5, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 175)
    - The Lambda: "Susie Bright to Address the Sexual State of the Union", March 1993 (Box 18, Folder 176)
    - The Rocket: "Susie Sexpert Explains It All For You", April 1993 (Box 18, Folder 177)
    - The Nation: "Text Sex", March 29, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 178)
    - "Sexy Talk Keeps Her In Demand", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 179)
    - OUT: "What Do Gay Men and Lesbians Want", April-May 1993 (Box 18, Folder 180)
    - Williamette Week: "Sex Appeal", March 18-24, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 181)
    - Voir: "L'Amour Braque", April 1993 (Box 18, Folder 182)
    - The Georgia Straight: "From Ellipses to Explicitness", December 4-11, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 183)
    - Newsweek: "Gay Clout: The New Power Brokers", May 3, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 184)
    - "The San Francisco Review of Books: Susie Bright's column "Cliterati", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 185)
    - Blue Stocking: "Why I Like Susie Bright", April 1993 (Box 18, Folder 186)
    - The Tartan: "Susie Bright Gives 'Sexpert' Advice", April 5, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 187)
    - Hour: "Susie Sexpert and the Feminist Pornographer", April 8-14, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 188)
    - SF Bay Guardian: "My Night With Susie Bright", May 7, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 189)
    - Future Sex: "Interview With the Sexpert", May 1993 (Box 18, Folder 190)
    - Outlines: "Snyde and Sneak", May 1993 (Box 18, Folder 191)
    - FAD: "Pia Sweden", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 192)
    - Just Out: "Countering Lesbian Erotic Illiteracy", May 15, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 193)
    - The Village Voice: "White Sex", May 18, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 194)
    - "The Year of the Lustful Lesbian" by Arlene Stein, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 195)
    - Vogue: "Goodybe to the Last Taboo", July 1993 (Box 18, Folder 196)
    - Metroline: "Susie Sells", June 24, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 197)
    - The New York Times: "She Knows What She Likes", July 11, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 198)
    - The Utne Reader: "The New Sexual Revolution", July-August 1993 (Box 18, Folder 199)
    - Empathy: "Dyke Porn Gets Me Wet", 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 200)
    - SF Weekly: "Victims and Masters", September 29, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - Penthouse Forum: "Clit Lit 101", October 1993 (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - OUT: "Gaydar", October-November 1993 (Box 18, Folder 203)
    - USA Today: "Lesbians in the Limelight", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 204)
    - Esquire Gentlemen: "What Women Love (and Hate) on Men", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - Library Journal, September 15, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 206)
    - SF Bay Times: "Susie Bright to Nan Parks: Get it Straight Girl!", October 21, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 207)
    - LA Reader Review: "The Joy of X", November 1993 (Box 18, Folder 208)
    - Boston Globe: "Paperback Best Seller", November 21, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 209)
    - Voice: "Words", November 23, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 210)
    - Advocate: "Fire Starter", November 17, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 211)
    - Express Books: "Intruder in the Lust", November 1993 (Box 18, Folder 212)
    - New Woman: "Dr. Ruth's Reading List", December 1993 (Box 18, Folder 213)
    - Playboy: State of the Union edition, December 1993 (Box 18, Folder 214)
    - Cliterati: "Reading, 'Riting, Rutting", November-December 1993 (Box 18, Folder 215)
    - City Pages: "Culture to Go", December 1, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 216)
    - The Boston Globe: "Sex Queen", December 17, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 217)
    - Esquire: "The Rise of 'Do Me' Feminism" and "How to Make Love to a Woman", February 1994 (Box 18, Folder 218)
    - Time out: "Susie Bright Tirelessly Champions the Woman's Sexual Point of View", January 21-27, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 219)
    - San Francisco Examiner: "The Best American Erotica 1993", January 16, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 220)
    - Express Books: "East Bay Bookshelf", February 1994 (Box 18, Folder 221)
    - NY Times: Letter tot eh Editor by Susie Bright, January 20, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 222)
    - Review: "San Francisco Chronicle Best-Sellers", February 20, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 223)
    - San Jose Mercury news: "Textual Gratification", February 20, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 224)
    - USA Today: "Literary Eroticism is Exciting INterest", February 10, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 225)
    - In These Times: "The Prime of Miss Catherine MacKinnon", March 7, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 226)
    - Adam: "Best American Erotica 1993", February 1994 (Box 18, Folder 227)
    - Review: "San Francisco Chronicle Best Sellers", March 6, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 228)
    - Newsday: "Feminist Forays Into Eroticism", April 20, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 229)
    - Cliterati: "Fermatize Me!", April-May 1994 (Box 18, Folder 230)
    - Publishers Weekly: "Herotica 3", April 11, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 231)
    - The New York Observer: "The Transom: Susie Bright's Bombproof Feminism", April 4, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 232)
    - German Press, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 233)
    - The Face: "Some Like It Hot", 1994 (Box 18, Folder 234)
    - The Advocate: "Have it your Way", May 31, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 235)
    - Boston Phoenix: "Butch is Back", May 1994 (Box 18, Folder 236)
    - Kirkus Reviews, March 15, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 237)
    - Windy City Times: "The PRime of Ms. Susie Bright", June 30, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 238)
    - Pacific Sun: "New Feminism", June 22-28, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 239)
    - Washington City Paper: "Pornocopia", June 24, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 240)
    - The Washington Blade: "Bright Ideas", July 29, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 241)
    - Los Angeles Times Magazine: "Susie Bright Tells All", July 24, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 242)
    - Austin American-Statesman: "War on Porn Divides Feminists", July 21, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 243)
    - Future Sex: "Jimi Hendrix Having Been Experienced and Why Little Dykes Understand", July 1994 (Box 18, Folder 244)
    - The Washington Blade: "Lust Between the Covers", August 26, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 245)
    - Publishers Weekly: "Paperbacks", September 26, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 246)
    - Kirkus Review: "In Brief", September 1, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 247)
    - New Woman: "X-tasy", September 1994 (Box 18, Folder 248)
    - The New York Times: "'People Like Me'", September 25, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 249)
    - Sebastopol Times: "American Erotica-In Review", October 1994 (Box 18, Folder 250)
    - Bazaar: "Word of Mouth", October 1994 (Box 18, Folder 251)
    - Esquire: "Can't We All Just Get It On", November 1994 (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - The Playboy Forum: "The Prince of Porn", 1994 (Box 18, Folder 253)
    - National Gallery, London: "Dirty Books", September 1994 (Box 18, Folder 254)
    - Ms.: "Tramped Up Charges", November-December 1994 (Box 18, Folder 255)
    - The Sonoma County Independent: "Lusty Bites", November 24-30, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 256)
    - The Independent: "Scholarly Conference Explores Pronography", November 3, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 257)
    - High Times: "Sex, Drugs and Susie Bright", November 1994 (Box 18, Folder 258)
    - Los Angeles Times: "'Erotique': Sexy Tales From Three Female Filmmakers", January 20, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 259)
    - Vanity Fair: "Vanities", February 1995 (Box 18, Folder 260)
    - Utne Reader: "100 Visionaries Who Could Change Your Life", January-February 1995 (Box 18, Folder 261)
    - The Monthly: "Critic's Choice", October 1995 (Box 18, Folder 262)
    - LA Reader/Weekly "Erotique" Reviews, January 1995 (Box 18, Folder 263)
    - Pure: "Pure's Woman of the Moment: Suzie Bright", February 1995 (Box 18, Folder 264)